翻译   半集不累桑
翻译   国士章鱼X
翻译   欧沈娜
翻译   肉松富士
翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
时间轴   Kallen
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
鸣谢   忙成狗的网飞
鸣谢   阿小小海
特效   草草
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第三季  第二集
第一夫人称  美军无关紧要
艾拉·萨伊德
发送短信
赛斯·格雷森
你在看发布会吗
道·斯坦普
在
结束之后
我可以过去吗
来吧
好  到时见
安德伍德总统宣布就业计划
正好你提到任人唯亲  参议员
I'm glad you brought up nepotism, Senator.
如果总统是直接任命
Um, if this were an outright appointment,
情况肯定不同
that would be one thing,
但他只能提名我而已
but in this case, the president can only nominate.
我的能力得由参议院认可
It's the Senate that deems me worthy.
我正是来博得你们的认可的
I'm here to convince you that I am.
不过说实话
Although, I must admit,
我丈夫上完厕所从不放下马桶圈
my husband never remembers to put the toilet seat down,
他也可能是想补偿我
so he could be trying to make it up to me.
我更担心的是你缺乏经验
My larger concern is your experience. You have very little.
十年前  我成立了个小慈善组织
Well, a decade ago, I founded a small nonprofit
后来影响力逐渐遍及全球
and I built it into a major global player.
我代表我的组织在国会通过了数项法案
I shepherded a number of bills through Congress on its behalf.
而去年一年
And over the last year,
我都致力于性侵法案改革
I've dedicated myself to sexual assault reform,
已经取得可喜进展
and have made meaningful strides.
虽然算不上治国才能
Now, while this may not qualify as statecraft,
但也表明了我的能力
it does illustrate my effectiveness,
我也希望在联合国发挥我的能力
the same effectiveness I plan on bringing to the United Nations.
谢谢  安德伍德夫人  我放弃我剩余的时间
Thank you, Mrs. Underwood. I yield the remainder of my time.
北达科塔州的华莱士夫人  您有八分钟
Uh, Mrs. Wallace of North Dakota, you have eight minutes.
谢谢  主席先生
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
安德伍德夫人  我细问一下
Mrs. Underwood, allow me to get specific.
您对联合国9214号决议
What is your take on UN Resolution 9214,
强行赦免刚果境内
the imposition of sanctions on the Congo for the--
非法采煤以及走私煤矿行为的看法吗
The illegal mining and smuggling of mineral resources.
是的  美国投了反对票
Yes. The United States voted against this resolution.
刚果共和国经济本就欠发达
The DRC is already wracked with economic hardship,
再加上政治局势不稳定
compounded by an unstable government.
煤矿几乎是唯一的人均GDP来源
It ranks 192 out of 194 in GDP per capita.
我认为我们应该鼓励外国资本进入
I think we need to encourage foreign investment
发展新的经济增长模式
and develop new forms of economic growth
而不是让刚果一穷到底
rather than make one of the world's poorest countries even poorer.
从国家安全角度考虑
From a national security perspective,
刚果的繁荣发展
the United States maintains
仍对美国是有利的
a strong interest in the success of the DRC.
-我们需要刚果稳定...  -他们来了
- We want a stable nation... - They're here.
...才能助我国对抗
...that can help us in combating the spread
极端伊斯兰分子在非洲的扩散  肆虐
of Islamic radicalism throughout the continent.
要做到这点  我们得做他们的盟友
And in order to achieve that, we need to work as its ally,
而不是监督人
not its disciplinarian.
早上好
Good morning.
总统先生
Mr. President.
杰姬
Jackie.
泰瑞
Terry.
坐吧
Shall we?
大纲你们都有了  今天要谈的是
Now you all have the, uh... overview. But what we have here today
-细化过的...  -先生  开始之前
- is the comprehensive breakdown-- - Sir, before we begin--
鲍勃  我知道你对法案还有疑虑
Look, Bob, I know you have some serious doubts about this program.
先让我把它亮出来
But just let me flesh it out first,
然后你有什么疑虑  我们再解决
and then I promise we can address any questions that you might have.
-总统先生  -一千万个岗位
- Uh, Mr. President-- - Ten million jobs.
大家都同意这对国家是好事吧
Can we all agree that that's a good thing for this country?
保障全体就业
Universal employment.
这是2016年留在白宫的关键
It's the key for our keeping the White House in 2016.
也是唯一赢回国会多数席位的机会
It's the only chance we have of winning back majorities in Congress.
离大选只有18个月
Now, the election's only 18 months away.
我们得做点大胆  坚决的事
We need to do something bold, something decisive.
给我党改头换面
We need to redefine our party.
我们想说的就是这个
Actually, that's what we wanted to discuss.
我党的确得改头换面
You're right, we do need to redefine the party.
换个新面孔
We need to do it with a fresh face.
我们不希望您参加2016大选
2016. We don't want you to run.
您本就不是民选的总统
You weren't even elected to the office in the first place.
之前的赦免很致命  支持率非常低
The pardons hurt you. Approvals are low.
我们不想怪谁  先生
We're not casting blame, sir.
只是为党的利益考虑
We just believe that this is best for the party.
我猜到会有这一天  但不是这么快
I suspected this was coming, but months from now.
我还希望到时候能拿出点成绩
I was hoping by then I'd have something to show for my efforts,
用进展打消他们的顾虑
that I could preempt their doubts with progress.
他们很紧张  这是冲动之举
They're nervous. They're being impulsive.
现在做这种决定太早了吧
It's a bit early to be deciding something like this.
等初选临近了再考虑吧
Shouldn't we revisit this when we're closer to the primaries?
你说呢  泰瑞
What do you think, Terry?
您也说了  我们离大选只有18个月了
Like you said, sir, we only have 18 months until the general.
离爱荷华州大选不到9个月了
Less than half of that to Iowa.
我们想尽快确定候选人
We would want to settle on a candidate soon.
全党一致支持的人
Someone who the whole party can get behind
就像共和党的门多萨
like the Republicans are getting behind Mendoza.
是谁呢
And who would that be?
还没讨论过
We haven't had a discussion on that yet.
我们出于尊重  先来找您
We came to you first, out of respect.
-总有几个人选吧  -还没有
- Well, there must be a shortlist. - No, not yet.
找到合适人选需要时间
It'll be a process to find the right person.
而我们希望您也能参与其中
And we were hoping that you would be a part of that process.
当然了我们只是请求  总统先生
Obviously, this is a request, Mr. President.
拍板的还是您
It's your decision.
但如果您决定参选  恕我们不能支持
But if you do run, sir, you won't have our support.
杰姬
Jackie?
我支持领导层的决定
I stand by the rest of the leadership.
好吧  还有许多事需要考虑
Well, this is certainly a lot to think about.
我们改天再聊《美国就业法案》的事
Let's table our discussion on America Works for another time,
不过感谢各位如此直率
but thank you all for being so forthright.
我稍后会就此问题给你们答复
I'll get back to you on this issue a little later on.
您介不介意我们先逗留一阵子
Would you like us to stick around for a while?
我们可不希望媒体觉得我们特地来跑一趟
We wouldn't want the press to think we came all the way here
-就为了五分钟的小会  -好想法
- for a five-minute meeting. - That's a very good idea.
不能引起非议
No raised eyebrows.
我会叫人送茶点到地图室的
I'll have some refreshments sent for you into the Map Room.
很好
Wonderful.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
作为上次会议性侵法案的主要支持者
As a vocal proponent for the Sexual Assault Bill last session,
你是否担忧你和美国军队的关系
are you concerned about your relationship with the US military?
我并不担心  参议员
No, I'm not, Senator.
我和参联会在那项法案上合作密切
I worked closely with the Joint Chiefs on that bill.
假设现在缅甸有一项维和行动
What if there were a peacekeeping mission in, say, Burma,
镇压平民暴动
to quell civil unrest,
联合国要求我国出兵
and the United Nations asked us to contribute troops,
让我们的男女士兵冒生命危险
to put our servicemen and women's lives in peril.
如果您用缅甸做假设的话
If you're using Myanmar as a hypothetical,
我觉得这一段时间内还不会发生  不过作为大使
I think we're a long way from that, but as Ambassador--
我的问题关注的是美国军力的使用
My question concerns the use of US military.
美军是无关紧要的  缅甸的现状是...
The US military is irrelevant. The current situation--
抱歉  安德伍德夫人  美军无关紧要吗
Excuse me, Mrs. Underwood. The US military is irrelevant?
我不是这个意思
Well, I-- That's not what I said.
这是你的原话  "美军是无关紧要的"
You said verbatim: "The US military is irrelevant."
我所想表达的意思是...
Well, in the, in the context of-- I meant...
这其中有许多...
uh, that there are plenty--
我对美国军人无比尊敬  先生
I have the utmost respect and appreciation for our troops, sir.
你这话可不像是有多尊敬
Not with statements like that, you don't.
参议员  请允许我解释
Senator, if I may, I can explain.
我们该怎么向海外服役的男女士兵
How do we explain to the men and women who serve,
那些出生入死的人解释
who put their lives on the line,
我们驻联合国的大使认为他们无关紧要
that our ambassador thinks they're irrelevant?
我觉得您这样说实在是曲解了我的本意
I think that's an unfair characterization of what I intended--
我可没有曲解什么  安德伍德夫人
I am not characterizing anything, Mrs. Underwood,
话是你自己说的
you said the words.
而现在你又想耍花招赖掉自己的话
And now you're trying to backpedal your way out of it.
-您就是在断章取义  -不要打断我
- You're trying to take my words-- - Don't interrupt me.
如果您能不打断我的话  我可以解释的
If you will stop interrupting me, I can explain--
瞧  问问题的是我们  你只管回答
No, you see, we ask the questions, you answer them.
而您就是不让我好好回答问题  参议员
You're not allowing me to answer the questions, Senator.
您只顾着哗众取宠  就是不肯听我讲
If you could maybe listen instead of grandstanding.
你此次应征的职位
The position you're being considered for
要求你有冷静沉稳的外交手段
requires calm, cool diplomacy.
相比你对军方的言论
What concerns me even more than the military comment
我们更担心你的举止
is your demeanor.
我们就要让你这样的人去当大使吗
Is this what we're to expect from our ambassador?
一个急性子
A hothead?
那请吧  安德伍德夫人  我洗耳恭听
Go ahead, Mrs. Underwood, I'm listening.
也许他们别有所图
Maybe it's leverage for another play.
先吓破我的胆  然后漫天要价
Scare the wits out of me and then come with the big ask.
你确定他们有价码吗
You sure there is one?
他们想毙掉《美国就业法案》
America Works. They want to kill it.
或者逼我考虑换一个总统竞选搭档
Or soften me up to consider another VP candidate for the ticket.
他们不喜欢布莱斯
They're no fans of Blythe.
什么事都有可能  没准要求多着呢
Could be anything, any combination of things.
-怎么了  -您还没看到吗
- What? - You saw it?
-看到什么  -第一夫人  先生
- Saw what? - The First Lady, sir.
天啊
Jesus.
我得赶紧打给她
I better call her.
她还在参加听证
She's still in the hearing, sir.
我要把整个过程看一遍  最好提前想想对策
I need to see this whole thing. Let's get ahead of it if we can.
-副检察长到了  -取消会面
- The Solicitor General is here. - Cancel it.
-您已经推迟两次了  -那再推迟一次
- You've already postponed twice. - Postpone it again.
不能再推迟了  先生
We can't put it off, sir.
还有不到一个月就要上最高法院了
It goes to the Supreme Court in less than a month.
我们有更大的事要处理
We have bigger fish to fry.
一名美国公民在无人机袭击中受伤
An American citizen was injured by a drone strike.
那是沃克下的令  不是我
That Walker authorized, not me.
但你是在任总统
But you're the sitting president.
如果处理不力  对你的权威会有极大损害
If we lose this, it undermines your authority.
媒体报道铺天盖地
The media is all over it.
我们必须跟副检察长统一说辞
We need our rhetoric in line with the Solicitor General's.
行了  老天爷  让她进来
All right. Christ! Send her in.
我会把片段放到您电脑上  方便您查阅
I'll put this clip on your computer, for when you're done.
私下联系泰瑞·乌麦克  我今天就要见他
Terry Womack. Today. Privately.
邓巴女士
Ms. Dunbar.
在我们开始前  有些话我要说清楚
Before we begin, I'd like to clear the air.
你的报告真的非常好  非常必要
Your report. You did good work, necessary work,
我对此表示敬意
and I admire you for it.
谢谢您的肯定  先生
I appreciate you saying that, sir.
你也理解我下达赦免令的考虑
And you understand the position I was in with the pardons.
那是政治问题  我不在行
That's politics, sir. Not my expertise.
那我们既往不咎了吗
What's past is past?
我关注的是要在法庭上说什么
My focus is the argument I'll present to the court.
她觉得我就是抢了银行逃到郡界的劫匪
She sees me as the bank robber who made it to the county line.
但她很聪明  没把这态度带进门
But she's smart enough to leave her badge at the door.
那么  这案子
So, the case.
先生  我们觉得以国家机密来辩护十分可行
As you know, sir, we think the State secret defense is strong.
我与中情局商议时...
When I consulted with the CIA on the--
我在想用国家机密做辩护是不是最好的策略
I'm wondering if State secrets is the best tactic.
默罕默德的两条腿都被截肢了
Both of Mahmoud's legs were amputated.
他会坐在轮椅上  出现在旁听席
He will be in the gallery, in his wheelchair.
这画面非常震撼
That's a powerful image.
就算是最高法院法官也会心软
Even Supreme Court Justices have hearts.
我们得让他们理性思考
We need to stay in their heads.
诉讼程序显然...
A procedural route is clearly-- -
稍等
Excuse me.
是的
Yes?
告诉她我得看点东西
Uh, tell her I need to watch something
两分钟后在书房给她回电
and I'll call her back from my study in two minutes.
-是我夫人  抱歉  -没关系
- It's my wife. I'm sorry. - Please.
-你只管回答  -而您就是不让我
- ...you answer them. - You're not allowing me
好好回答问题  参议员
to answer questions, Senator.
您只顾着哗众取宠
Maybe you would benefit more
就是不肯听我讲
from listening than grandstanding.
我刚看完  我能做什么
I just watched. How can I help?
我在给各个参议员打电话
I'm calling Senators.
如果你也给他们打就太过了
I think it would be heavy-handed if you did too.
你生气我能理解
Well, I don't blame you for getting upset.
-你不应该受如此对待  -我成靶子了
- You didn't deserve that. - I'm a target now.
-这是从政的代价  -我们都是靶子
- That's the price of admission. - We both are.
领导层不希望我参加竞选
The leadership, they don't want me to run.
-什么  -他们是这么说的
- What? - Yeah, that's what they said
我都没来得及拿出法案
before I could even present the program.
-这么快吗  -是啊  我也很惊讶
- This soon? - Yeah, that's what surprised me.
-整个领导层吗  -所有人  包括杰姬
- The entire leadership? - All of them, including Jackie.
-这女人毫无忠心  -等着看吧
- That woman has no sense of loyalty. - Well, we'll see.
我要和乌麦克见面  让他改主意
I'm gonna meet with Womack. Turn him around.
他们只是人多势众
They only have strength in numbers.
请继续
Continue, please.
正如之前所说  我们的程序性抗辩很可行
As I was saying, we think our procedural defense is strong.
国家机密不允许被用作证据
State secrets prohibit the introduction of evidence.
即使他们不直接撤案
Assuming they won't dismiss outright,
辩论也会聚焦于遵从行政命令
the argument will focus on deference to the executive.
法院和外交政策的独立性
Separation between the courts and foreign policy.
我们面对来自多领域的威胁
They simply don't have the security intelligence
他们根本没有足够的安全情报
to second-guess covert operations
事后指戳秘密行动的合理性
while we're facing threats on multiple fronts.
先生
Sir?
-我现在无法处理  -您说什么  先生
- I can't do this now. - Excuse me, sir?
我的办公室会与你联系  抱歉  谢谢
My office will be in touch. Apologies. Thank you very much.
您只顾着哗众取宠  就是不肯听我讲
Maybe you would benefit more from listening than grandstanding.
欢迎收看CNN首席国会记者
Joining me now from Capitol Hill,
达娜·巴什从国会发来的报道
CNN's Chief Congressional Correspondent, Dana Bash.
达娜  现在国会意向如何
Dana, what is the mood at the Capitol?
没错  我理解
Right, I understand, but...
已经有几位参议员公开表示
We already have several Senators publicly saying
由于安德伍德夫人的言论
that they're gonna vote against Mrs.Underwood
将会投票反对她
because of her comments.
而另一些参议员
A number of others I've spoken to
从支持她
have gone from supporting her...
-好的  -转变为了持观望态度
- Right. - ...nomination, to being on the fence.
但达娜  她说的对吧
But, Dana, she's correct, isn't she?
门多萨就是在哗众取宠
Mendoza was grandstanding.
也许吧  但即便如此  看看支持率
Maybe. But even so, if you look at the numbers here,
这事杀伤力很大
this is doing real damage.
投票结果本就接近
The vote was always going to be close...
是的
Yes.
第一夫人的形势可不太好
...things aren't looking good for the First Lady.
-我明白  但  -她对美军的言论会是
- No, I understand, but-- - Could her military remark be...
-门多萨来电  -口误吗
- It's Mendoza. - ...a slip of the tongue?
感谢您接听  参议员  希望您能再考虑
I appreciate your time, Senator. I hope you'll reconsider.
-他在线吗  -没错
- He's on now? - Yes.
把电视关了
Turn that off?
参议员  感谢你回电
Senator, hi. Thank you for returning my call.
抱歉让你等这么久  我要处理一堆采访
Sorry it took so long. I had a ton of interview requests.
我想表示道歉
I just wanted to apologize
我今天无意失敬
if I came across as disrespectful in any way.
我不该那么说
That was wrong of me.
我知道你是无心的  克莱尔
I know you didn't mean it, Claire.
很不幸事情发展至此
It's just unfortunate how things are playing out.
我知道你本人不能给我投票
I realize you can't vote for me yourself,
但我希望也许
but I was hoping that maybe
你可以帮我说些好话
you would say something to the effect to--
什么  对媒体吗
What, to the press?
-或者私下里  对你同事  -不行
- Or even privately, to your colleagues. - I can't do that.
参议员  投票应该注重于我的优点
Senator, the vote should center on my merits,
而不是你我剑拔弩张的个别瞬间
not a few moments where you and I took the gloves off.
我觉得这很能说明问题
Well, I think that was telling, don't you?
你面对压力时的反应
How you behaved under pressure?
参议员  你知道你是在断章取义吧
Senator, you know you were taking out of context what I said.
知道  我故意惹怒你的
Of course I was. I was trying to rile you up.
我也成功了
And I succeeded.
我真后悔
I wish I hadn't,
因为你现在的情况真的不乐观
because it's gonna make things really tough for you.
但是如果你现在
But, if you can convince my
还能说服我的同事改变主意的话
colleagues to change their minds despite that...
你肯定能做个好大使的
why, you'd make a great Ambassador.
-叨扰了  参议员  -好运  克莱尔
- Thank you for your time, Senator. - Good luck, Claire.
真是个王八蛋
He's a son of a bitch.
试试彼得森
Let's try Peterson next.
支持率总会变化
Approvals go up and down.
我们不能被公众的想法左右
We can't allow ourselves to be held hostage by public opinion.
是共和党在逼我们
We're being held hostage by the Republicans.
由你代表我党是击败不了他们的  就这样
We can't beat them with you as the face of the party. Period.
你们真的考虑清楚了吗
Have you all really thought this through?
我是在任总统
I'm a sitting president.
但不是民选的
But not an elected one.
但就这么放弃在任者
But still, to abandon the incumbent,
和其所代表的影响力吗
and all the advantages that that entails?
问题就在这儿  你没什么影响力了
Which is the problem. We don't see any advantages.
如果你跟我们的路线走
And if you were to come on board with us,
公开宣布你不参选
if you were to announce that you're not running,
大家就不会觉得是我们抛弃了你
it wouldn't seem as if we're abandoning you.
党还是统一的
The party looks unified.
自从我强行通过教育法案
Bob Birch has been trying to do me in
鲍勃·博奇就一直计划着坑我一把
since I forced the Education Bill down his throat.
他是在用站不住脚的道理说服你们
I think he's using shaky logic to get you all on board
方便他向我寻仇
so he can carry out some personal vendetta.
是我的主意
It was my idea.
不是鲍勃的
Not Bob's.
希望你能跟我们合作
I hope you work with us.
我们说的是真心话
We meant it when we said it.
我们希望听取你的意见
We would like for you to be a part of the conversation.
-喂  -是我
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.
-我听不见  -等等
- I can't hear you. - Hang on a second.
-赛斯吗  -对
- Seth? - Yeah.
我就想问问你有没有事
I was just calling to check in. See how things are going.
没事  都挺好的
Good. Things are going really good.
等一下
Hey, hold on one quick second.
我知道
Listen, uh, I know
你们要推出《美就法》项目了
you're rolling out the AmWorks program soon.
雷米肯定已经有了计划
I'm sure Remy has a plan in place,
但我也列了个单子
but I've been putting together a list.
关键议员
Some key representatives
和他们可能开出的价码
and what they might want in exchange for support.
肮脏秘密什么的
Skeletons in the closet, that kind of thing.
那项法案现在搁置了
Yeah, that's on hold for the moment.
-不推出了吗  -就是暂时搁置了
- You're not rolling it out? - It's just on hold.
-出什么事了吗  -没什么事
- Is something up? - No, everything's fine.
现在的重点是下周俄罗斯的峰会
We're focused on the summit next month with Russia.
你还好吗  身体好起来了吗
But you're good? You getting stronger?
-嗯  -精神呢
- Yeah. - In good spirits?
好得不得了
Never been better.
我发邮件给你  他的想法记得告诉我
I'll email you my ideas. Let me know what he says.
-没问题  -谢谢
- Will do. - Thanks.
参议员  上周在办公室见面时
Senator, when we met in your office last week,
我们进行了一次很长很有成果的谈话
we had a long, productive conversation.
我觉得听证会上的十秒说明不...
I can't imagine ten seconds during the hearing would--
参议员先生  我五分钟后再打过去好吗
Senator, may I call you back in five minutes?
谢谢
Thank you.
-弗兰西斯  -不行  根本是他的主意
- Francis? - No luck. It was his idea.
你打算怎么做
What are you going to do?
找上次竞选前50的资助人
Top 50 bundlers from last cycle.
控制了资金我就不必靠领导层了
I don't need the leadership if I can get the money.
-你呢  -还没准
- You? - Too early to tell.
我就在这儿  需要就来找我
Well, I'm here if you need me.
我一直说权力比金钱重要
I've always said that power is more important than money.
但竞选的时候  金钱才能让权力
But when it comes to elections, money gives power...
有竞争力
well, a run for its money.
弗兰西斯·安德伍德
It's Francis Underwood.
你说他挺帅的来着
I thought you said he was handsome.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
如果她没收到说有"急事"的短信
Well, if she doesn't receive a text with the word "urgent,"
那就算不上约会了
it's not an official date.
你好  艾伦·库克
How are you? Alan Cooke.
-雷米·丹顿  -幸会
- Remy Danton. - Nice to meet you.
我去...打几个电话
I'm just gonna go, uh... take a few calls.
我替你点了杯咖啡
There's an espresso coming with your name on it, okay?
再会
Nice meeting you.
说说吧
So here we are.
我没有参与  会面十分钟前他们才通知我
I wasn't part of the decision. They told me ten minutes before.
他们都找谁谈竞选的事了
Who are they talking to? About running?
据我所知还没有
No one yet, as far as I can tell.
总得有个名单  哪怕还没说出来
There has to at least be a list. Even a mental one.
有些想法
Some ideas.
我们需要你查出来
We need you to find out.
沃克辞职的时候
You know, when Walker resigned,
弗兰克就任总统  你是幕僚长
Frank's president, you're Chief of Staff.
-我呢  -你还在领导层
- But me? - You're still in the leadership.
-助理党鞭  -就是扯淡
- Assistant Whip. - It's a bullshit title.
我不在核心圈子里
I'm out of the inner circle.
那你要什么
What do you want?
我要做他的副总统
I want to be on the ticket. His VP.
我们只要一点点信息
All we want is a little information.
你开的价  太高了吧
What you're asking is... disproportionate.
当做是还债了吧
It's repaying a debt.
好大一笔债呢  弹劾法案是我搞定的
A big one. I whipped the votes for impeachment.
现在我要回报了
I should get to cash in on that.
他是不会同意的
There's no way he'll go for this.
那我也没必要做你们的眼线了
Then there's no reason for me to be your eyes and ears.
回头联系你
I'll get back to you.
要在工作时间
During business hours.
不  马克  就在白宫的决策室  我发誓
No, Mark, we ran it in the White House screening room and I swear to God,
战斗机撞向海狼核潜艇的时候
when those jets crashed into one of our Seawolf subs,
参联会都喊出来了
the Joint Chiefs screamed.
他们肯定不希望你用  更不会免费给你
No, they didn't want you to use it and certainly not for free.
大卫  我不只是要钱
David, I'm not just asking you for money,
我希望你做我的竞选主席
I'm asking you to be one of my campaign chairmen.
那可比在总统卧室睡一晚风光多了
That buys you a lot more than a night in the Lincoln Bedroom.
克莱尔·安德伍德找海尔布鲁克参议员
Claire Underwood for Senator Hylbrook.
我同意  肯定不能只靠安全委员会的支持
I agree. We can never rely solely upon Security Counsel support.
斯科特  还剩18个月了
Scott, we're 18 months out.
你想参与进来
Now, if you wanna be on the ground floor,
就别想占着茅坑不拉屎
you got to shit or get off the pot.
关键是领导  做出榜样
The key is to provide leadership, to lead by example.
我还想着一起去梅德斯通打打高尔夫呢
I was hoping we could hit Maidstone for a quick eighteen.
当然不  我打得可差了
No, I'm a terrible golfer.
是啊  你就可以打败总统了
Exactly, you'd have the pleasure of beating a president.
以后跟人可有得讲了
Now wouldn't that be a good cocktail story?
我和您委员会里的共和党人差不多都谈过了
I've spoken to almost every Republican in your committee, sir.
他们说都听您的
Yes, they're taking their cue from you.
还有别的号码可以联系上他吗
Is there another number where I can reach him?
我今晚一定要跟他谈谈
It's important that we speak this evening.
是的  不管多晚
Yes, anytime, no matter how late.
汤姆  我只希望你多点信心
A little faith, Tom. That's all I'm asking.
是啊  我也不喜欢别人叫我女士
Oh, yes! I know, I don't like being called "Ma'am" Either.
要是我做什么事都得哄大伙开心
If I made every decision based on what makes people feel good,
那我就去主持脱口秀了  当什么总统
I'd be a talk show host, not the president.
我知道詹宁斯上将是你的好朋友
Well, I know Admiral Jennings is a good friend of yours,
-我可以亲自打给他  -别被恐惧左右
- I can call him personally. - Don't let fear drive you.
你的生意不是这么做出来的吧
That's not how you run your business, is it?
我知道你也曾被人曲解
I know you've been in my shoes,
那种断章取义不是我们本意
and sound bites are not who we are.
那是省小钱吃大亏
Penny-wise and pound-foolish.
抱歉  参议员  吵醒你了吗
I'm so sorry, Senator, did I wake you?
好的  没事  我明天再挂
Yes, no, I'll try back again tomorrow.
你目光短浅我不怪你
I can't fault you for being shortsighted.
但我记性好你也别怪我
I hope you won't fault me for having a long memory.
晚安
Good night!
已经有人睡了  我明早再试
I'm waking people up now. I'll start again in the morning.
-怎么样  -一点也说不准
- How's it looking? - I had to flip a coin? I don't know.
-你呢  -还没人支持我
- You? - Not a single backer yet.
-一个都没有吗  -加州那边还早
- Not one? - California's still awake.
也许我在西海岸运气能好点
Maybe I'll have better luck out west.
我出去跑一圈  我得做点什么
I'm going for a run. I need to do something.
-太晚了  -我闲不下来了
- It's late. - Well, I'm too restless.
那我一个人在这儿吃晚饭了
Well, I'll be here, singing for my supper.
求个脸书上的毛头小子
It's humiliating to have to beg from some kid who was on Facebook
实在丢人  但那是...
before his testicles descended, but that's--
德里克  弗兰西斯·安德伍德  有时间吗
Derrick, Francis Underwood. Do you have a few minutes?
我绕着国家广场跑
I'll be running along the Mall tonight.
那要出动全套安保
That requires a full detail.
你们多久能准备好
How soon can you be ready?
我们更希望您在附近跑
We'd far prefer you ran on the track.
我去国家广场跑
I'll be running along the Mall.
好的  夫人  第一夫人安保尽快出动
Yes, ma'am. We're going to need the First Lady's detail, ASAP.
-不可公开  -可以
- This is off the record. - Agreed.
过去六个月
You've called my office every day
你一直给我办公室打电话  问同一个问题
for the last six months with one question.
领导层的人我都联系过
I call everyone in the leadership.
得到的都是同一套说辞
I get the same non-answer from all of you:
"弗兰克·安德伍德是现任总统"
"Frank Underwood is our president..."
我们是他坚实的后盾
He has our undivided support.
博奇有次说错了
Birch slipped up once.
他说"不可动摇"不是"坚实"
He said "unwavering" instead of "undivided."
我还以为他嗑药了
I wanted to drug-test him.
今早在白宫有过一次会面
There was a meeting this morning in the White House.
你们出来时我看到了
I was there on Pebble Beach when you came out.
一共就谈了四分半
It lasted four and a half minutes.
-你们进去了一个小时  -是待了一个小时
- You were in there for an hour. - We were inside for an hour.
但不代表就谈了一个小时
Doesn't mean the meeting lasted that long.
发生什么了  为什么这么快
What happened? Why so short?
你入围过普利策奖呢
You're the Pulitzer finalist.
《美国就业法案》吗
America Works?
总统下午是为了这个去的国会山吗
Is that why the president went to the Capitol this afternoon?
白宫的人都不松口
No one from the White House would say.
晚安
Have a good night.
你选了我  你想干什么
You chose me. What's your play?
只要是写总统的  人们都会关注
When you write about presidents, people pay attention.
得最后定胜负了
It'll come down to the wire.
我有信心  但我也不希望有什么事听天由命
I'm confident, but I don't want to leave anything to chance.
据艾瑞克森的消息  我今早有47票了
Well, according to Erikson, I have 47 votes as of this morning.
我知道  参议员  但那还不够
Well, I know, Senator, but that's not enough.
我还需要您的票
I need yours.
我绝对是要竞选总统的
I have every intention of running for president.
我得确定你们是支持我的
I need to know you two are with me.
有任何疑虑  就现在说出来
If you have any doubts, now's the time to let me know.
南茜  清空时间表
Nancy, wipe the schedule clean.
全推掉
Yes, everything.
不讨论出个计划就不出去
We don't leave this office until we have a plan.
夫人  复活节滚彩蛋游戏的事
Ma'am? The Easter Egg Roll we were scheduled for?
-是啊  -如果不方便...
- Right. - If this is a bad time...
没什么  进来吧
No, that's fine. Please, come in.
你好
Hello?
是的  克莱尔·安德伍德  他在等我电话
Yes... Claire Underwood. He's expecting my call.
你好  希拉  真美
Hi, Sheila. They're beautiful.
摆一下好吗
Would you mind setting them up, please?
我还要打几个电话
I have a couple more calls to make.
参议员  我挺好  您好吗
Hello, Senator. Yes, I'm well. How are you?
提名华盛顿特区克莱尔·安德伍德
The nomination of Claire Underwood, of Washington DC,
担任美利坚合众国
to be the Representative of
驻联合国代表
the United States of America to the United Nations.
请听书记官喊名字  投赞成和反对
Yeas and nays have been ordered and the clerk will call the roll.
-阿博纳先生  -赞成
- Mr. Abner. - Yea.
博朗先生
Mr. Braun.
布雷先生
Mr. Bray.
-这个太粉了  -小姑娘都喜欢粉色
- This one's a little too pink. - Girls like pink.
这可不止是粉色了  几乎是霓虹色了
This is more than pink. It's neon.
-我要选四个吗  -是的  夫人
- Uh, I'm choosing four? - Yes, ma'am.
-薇拉  -领先两票  48对46
- Willa? - Up by two: 48 to 46.
-夫人  我们可以稍后再做  -不用
- Ma'am, we can finish up later. - No.
-下面呢  -纪念彩蛋
- Uh, what's next? - The commemoratives.
都很特别
These are really special.
黑蛋吗
A black egg?
-有爱国元素点缀  -那也是黑蛋
- Yes, with patriotic tipping. - It's still a black egg.
刻着美国总统与第一夫人的签名
Engraved with POTUS and FLOTUS signatures.
夫人  最后结果  52对48
Ma'am? Final tally: 52 to 48.
反对占多
Against.
-媒体呢  -在通气室
- The press? - In the briefing room.
我就回来  稍等一下好吗
I'll just be a few minutes. Would you mind waiting?
当然  夫人
Not at all, ma'am.
我听说了
I just heard.
真遗憾
I'm so sorry.
媒体等着呢
The press is waiting.
他们等去吧
Well, they can wait.
要我陪你去吗
Do you want me to come with you?
不用  我就想尽快了事
No. I just want to get it over with.
克莱尔  你...
Claire. You--
早上好
Good morning.
参议院没有通过我的提名
Naturally, I'm disappointed
我自然很失望
that the Senate did not confirm my nomination today.
但能得到这个机会  我已经很感激
But I'm very grateful to have been afforded the opportunity.
我自然要谢谢我的丈夫
I'd be remiss if I did not thank my husband
感谢他对我的支持与信任
for all the faith and trust he placed in me.
他一向支持我实现梦想
He's always supported me in achieving my goals.
我期待继续履行第一夫人的职责
I look forward to continued service as First Lady.
谢谢
Thank you.
选绿的  蓝的  和米色的吧
Um, let's go with the... green, the blue, and the cream.
纪念彩蛋呢  可以说是金券
And for the rare one? The Golden Ticket, so to speak?
红的  红的好看
Red. That one's beautiful.
谢谢  我先走了
Thank you. Excuse me, please?
你试过吗
You ever try to do this?
让蛋立住
Balance an egg?
我们小时候常玩
We used to do this as kids.
物理法则是没法改的吧
You can't change the laws of physics, can you?
我错了  太难了
I was wrong. It's too hard.
先生
Sir?
对抗领导层  筹集竞选资金
Fighting the leadership, raising money.
不能强迫他们做极不情愿的事
We can't get them to do what they're dead set against doing.
现在是负分  要拉到零都需要六个月
We'd need six months just to get them back to square one.
得逆向思维
We have to reverse our thinking.
当强风袭来的时候
When the wind's blowing at gale force,
没有必要逆风航行
there's no point in sailing against it.
您有什么主意
What do you have in mind?
请接白宫法律顾问办公室
The White House Counsel's office, please.
我不管他们有什么安排
I don't care about their schedules.
今天凑不齐那就明天早上
If not today, tomorrow morning.
我们还请杰姬来吗
Should I invite Jackie, too?
她毕竟还算是领导层里的
Well, she qualifies as leadership.
-那她的条件呢  -先拖着
- What about her ask? - Stall her for now.
看看会面怎样再说
Let's see how the meeting goes.
你给我写份讲稿  要字斟句酌
I want you to write the speech, every word.
-好的  先生  -不得外泄
- Yes, sir. - And no leaks.
三小时内给您草稿
You'll have a draft in three hours.
另外  道格给我发了份《美就法》的游说策略
And, sir... Doug emailed me a lobbying strategy for AmWorks.
-您要看一看吗  -他自己写的吗
- Do you want to look at it? - Of his own accord?
-你没告诉他吧  -我什么都没说
- You didn't tell him? - No, I didn't say a word.
肯定是他看新闻自己琢磨出来的
It must be what he gathered from watching the news.
-他怎样了  -道格听起来还行
- How is he? - Uh, Doug seems fine.
按您的要求  我一直在给他打电话
I've been calling him, like you asked.
-但他看起来如何  -他告诉我一切都好
- But he seems all right? - Well, he tells me things are good,
不过我估计就算不好他也不会说的
although I don't think he'd admit it if they weren't.
不如你抽空去看看他  我抽不出身
Why don't you stop by from time to time, since I can't.
-要亲眼见到他  -好的  先生
- See him in person. - Yes, sir.
把他的策略转给我
And send me his email.
克莱尔
Claire?
如果你找我  我就在书房
I'll be in my study if you need me.
你忙什么呢
What're you working on?
-给你带了杯咖啡  -你可救了我的命了
- Brought you a coffee. - My savior.
党领导层昨天开了个会
The leadership meeting yesterday morning.
只持续了四分半
It lasted four and a half minutes.
你从哪听说的
Where'd you hear that?
这么重大的内政议题不可能这么快就否了
That's not long enough to reject a major domestic agenda.
我又没出席  我怎么知道会开了多久
I wasn't in the meeting. I don't know how long it lasted.
-出了什么事  -随你怎么说了
- Something went down. - If you say so.
反正我是什么都没听说
Uh, I didn't hear anything about it.
没准是总统有急事先走了
Could've been the president was called away.
-经常这样  -这次不是
- That happens all the time. - Not this time.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
显然我有个知道的比你多的消息源
Clearly, I have a source that knows more than you.
大多数消息源都这样  至少是假装这样
Most sources do. At least they pretend they do.
多谢你的咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
加两包糖  我下次会记得的
Two sugars next time. I'll remember that.
你和艾拉·萨伊德谈过了
You talked to Ayla Sayyad.
我既可以帮忙也可以帮倒忙
I can either be an asset or a liability.
你以为这样就能保你成为竞选搭档了吗
You think this puts you on the ticket now?
你去告密的话自然不会了
Not if you tell him.
不过比较聪明的选择是替我说好话
But the smart move would be to advocate on my behalf.
别逼我  杰姬
Don't strong-arm me, Jackie.
你是中间人  不逼你逼谁
You're the man in the middle. Who else would I strong-arm?
我想成为你们的一员  雷米
I want to be on your team, Remy.
我们合作的时候结果一向不错
We do well when we're on the same team.
你还有别的电话吗
You have more calls?
没有  忙完了
No. I'm done.
-谁向她泄密了  -我不知道  先生
- Who spoke to her? - I have no idea, sir.
-你的工作就是知道  -事情发展太快
- Well, it's your job to know. - Things are moving fast.
我只想尽力控制局面
I'm just trying to stay ahead of them.
我们动作得再快点  会面定下来了吗
Well, we need to move faster. Has the meeting been set?
明早8点  博奇的办公室刚给我回了话
Eight AM tomorrow. I just heard back from Birch's office.
很好  联系媒体准备好9点直播
Good. Let's have the networks ready to go live by nine.
还有个问题  杰姬
One more thing. Jackie.
我觉得你最好尽快做决定
I think you should decide sooner rather than later.
如果我们走这条路
If we're gonna go this route,
就得争取尽可能多的友军
we need every ally we can get.
等开完会  我们再谈
After the meeting. We'll discuss then.
你起来了啊
You've emerged.
我小睡了一觉  昨晚我都没怎么睡
I took a nap. Last night was... I didn't get much sleep.
我也是
Me, neither.
我们肯定会给你找个职位的
We're gonna find something for you.
其它的职位  或作为第一夫人的职责  我保证
Some other position, or something as First Lady, I promise.
我知道
I know.
-你不睡做什么  -我在忙我的演说
- What are you doing up? - I've got to go over my speech.
我准备明晚发表演讲
It's happening tomorrow night.
什么演讲
What speech?
有点太急了  不是吗
It's premature, isn't it?
读下去
Read on.
好吗
Yes?
好
Yes.
谢谢  请坐
Thank you. Please.
你们的请求  我想了很多
I put a great deal of thought into what you've all asked of me.
我让自己尽量保持开放的态度
I challenged myself to keep an open mind.
而我的决定是  我将不参选下任总统
And my decision is: I will not run for president.
他们觉得这好的不真实  也的确不是真的
Look, they're thinking it's too good to be true, and it is.
我之前在椭圆办公室撒过谎
I lied in the Oval Office before.
这次不想再触霉头
I didn't want to take the chance this time.
万一真说中了可不好
It's too big a deal to jinx myself.
今晚9点
At nine o'clock tonight,
我就向全国宣布我的决定
I will announce to the nation my decision.
你什么目的
What's the catch?
我要大家来这里见面是有原因的
I wanted us to meet here in this room for a reason.
过去五个月
For the past five months,
我的团队就坐在这儿  起草《美国就业法案》
my team has sat at this very table, developing America Works.
你们知道这项目对我意义重大
You know how much the program means to me,
我希望你们也能像我一样重视
and I want it to mean as much to you.
-那你是有目的的了  -不  是机遇
- So there is a catch. - No, an opportunity.
我们都知道
Look, we all know the--
单纯地打个比方
All right, let's just say for... argument's sake
这张桌子
that this table here
就是未来一年半
represents the next year and a half, all right?
我们在这儿
So, this is us right now.
那边的尽头是大选
And down there at the end, that's the election.
我要是决定竞选  接下来几个月我就得筹款
Now, if I did run, I'd spend the next few months fundraising.
到这时左右  我要正式宣布
And then somewhere around here, I'd formally announce.
哪怕我赢了党内竞选
And then even if I did win the nomination,
比如说在这个时候
say, somewhere around here,
我就得面对
I'd start to have to face off
共和党的对手  很可能是门多萨
with a Republican challenger, probably Mendoza.
那可就是真刀真枪了
And then things would get brutal.
每天都得去做活动
Daily, daily events.
防御对手的进攻
Fending off attacks.
同时进攻对手
Launching my own.
你们说得对
And... you're right.
最后...
In the end...
...我可能会输
...I'd probably lose.
我会花18个月的时间竞选
I would spend 18 months campaigning,
就没有时间治国了
which would leave no time to govern.
你们让我看清了局势
But you have opened my eyes.
解放了思想
I feel liberated.
接下来的18个月我想专注一件事
I want to spend these next 18 months dedicated to one thing:
《美国就业法案》  但我需要你们的帮助
America Works. But I need your help to do it.
你开的价码有点高啊  总统先生
You're putting an awfully big price tag on this, Mr. President.
不  是你们开了高额价码
No, you've put an awfully big price tag on this.
你们要我占18个月的位子
You're asking me to be a placeholder for 18 months
而我想治国
and I intend to govern.
如果《美国就业法案》成功了
And if America Works succeeds,
那不管16年谁来竞选
then whoever you choose to run in 2016
都会有全党的支持
not only has the backing of a united party,
更会有一笔可贵的遗产
but a formidable legacy.
社会保障呢  社会福利呢
But Social Security? Benefits. Entitlements.
我们可不想推选个新人
We don't want to present a fresh face
反过来坑了自己
only to shoot ourselves in the foot.
那就别假装全党统一了
Then let's not pretend to unite the party,
让全党统一支持这项法案吧
let's unite the party behind this legislation.
肯定过不了共和党那关
We'll never get it past the Republicans.
我们不是来谈判的
We are not here to negotiate!
你要放眼未来吗  鲍勃  快放眼看啊
You want forward-thinking, Bob? Then think forward.
想16年推举个新人吗  想通力合作吗
You want a fresh face for 2016? You wanna work together?
把我的法案递交给国会吧
Then present my program to Congress.
如果通不过  那也没办法
And if it dies there, so be it.
但我们至少他妈该试一下
But I want us to fucking try!
我打算让位了
I am prepared to vacate this chair.
你们也妥协一下
Meet me halfway.
很快
Any moment now,
总统就将在东厅向全国发表直播讲话
the president will be addressing the nation live from the East Room.
关于总统讲话的内容
The White House has remained silent
白宫一直闭口不谈
on the subject of the president's speech,
但国会有消息称  是关于近几个月来
but sources in Congress say it will focus on the jobs initiative
总统一直在筹备的就业法案
he's been planning to unveil for several months.
该法案被称作《美国就业法案》
The program, dubbed America Works,
一直在秘密起草中
was developed in secret.
具体细节尚不明了
Any details are the by-product of speculation,
但有消息称  该法案
but sources suggest it will have elements
既有激进的内容  又有保守的成分
from both liberal and conservative agendas.
而共和党控制的国会
What remains to be seen
会不会通过该法案
is whether a Republican-controlled Congress
就拭目以待了
will cooperate in pushing the program forward.
自本届国会成立以来  共和党一直
The White House has faced significant opposition from the GOP
激烈反对白宫
since Congress began its current session,
很多人也推测
and many speculate
总统肆意行使否决权
that the president's liberal application of veto power
可能会导致国会高层
may leave congressional leaders disinclined
不愿支持他的法案
to support this new jobs program.
另外  自党鞭时期就支持安德伍德总统的
Additionally, many Democratic supporters of President Underwood,
部分民主党人士
from his days as House Majority Whip,
也在去年11月离开了国会
were voted out of office in November,
让总统在立法上的影响力进一步降低
diminishing his personal influence over legislators.
安德伍德政府的低支持率
Low approval ratings are a continuing concern
一直是个问题
for the Underwood administration.
国会内有消息称
And congressional sources suggest
处理失业问题
the choice to tackle unemployment
也许正是16年大选的策略
may be part of a campaign strategy for 2016.
最近有民调显示
Recent polls indicate that
不到三分之一美国人
less than one third of all Americans say they would
愿考虑投给安德伍德总统
consider voting for President Underwood...
...提高就业率仍是
...job growth has remained
总统竞选的热门话题
a popular platform in national elections,
如果今天的讲话能受好评
and if today's announcement is received well,
安德伍德总统的
President Underwood's
竞选肯定有机会因此受益
campaign certainly has an opportunity to benefit.
谢谢
Thank you.
先生  我们五秒后开始
Sir, we're ready for you in five seconds.
晚上好
Good evening.
一直以来  我们华盛顿的人都没说实话
For too long, we in Washington have been lying to you.
我们说为人民服务
We say we're here to serve you,
但实际上  我们却自私自利
when in fact, we're serving ourselves.
为什么  因为我们只想着连任
And why? We are driven by our own desire to get reelected.
我们渴望继续执政而忽视了治国之职
Our need to stay in power eclipses our duty to govern.
今晚  这到此为止
That ends tonight.
今晚  我告诉你们实话
Tonight, I give you the truth.
实话就是
And the truth is this:
美国梦让你们失望了
The American dream has failed you.
努力工作  遵守规则  不保证你们能成功
Work hard? Play by the rules? You aren't guaranteed success.
你们孩子的生活不会比你们好
Your children will not have a better life than you did.
一千万美国人非常想
Ten million of you can't even get a job,
找工作却找不到
even though you desperately want one.
我们被社保  医保  医疗补助  社会福利
We've been crippled by Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid,
所牵绊
by welfare, by entitlements.
这才是问题的根源  福利
And that is the root of the problem: entitlements.
我说明白了  没有天生的福利
Let me be clear. You are entitled to nothing.
没有天生的福利
You are entitled to nothing.
美国的根基是勤劳精神
America was built on the spirit of industry.
未来靠自己努力  而非靠人施予
You build your future. It isn't handed to you.
华盛顿的问题
And the problem with Washington
在于没有给你们打造生活的工具
is that we haven't given you the tools to build it.
政府为人民服务的唯一办法
The only way for us to serve you
就是想办法让你们服务自己
is to give you the means to serve yourselves.
这就是我想要做的
Well, that's exactly what I intend to do.
不施舍  而是给工作
Not handouts. Jobs.
实实在在的工作
Real paying jobs.
在未来几周  民主党领导人
In the next few weeks, the Democratic leadership
会提出一个叫《美国就业法案》的项目
will introduce a program called "America Works."
其目的很简单
Its goal is simple:
让一千万没有工作的美国人有工作
to put the ten million Americans who are unemployed to work.
每一个想工作的人都会有工作
All of them. If you want a job, you get one.
这需要五千亿美元
The cost is five hundred billion dollars.
这个数目很庞大
Now, that's a lot of money.
为了这笔钱  我们得完全重新思考
To pay for it, we'll need to rethink Social Security,
社保  医保和福利政策
healthcare and benefits from the ground up.
我们不能维持现有的福利政策
We can't maintain the welfare state as we know it.
这么说很不讨人喜欢
Now, that's not a popular thing to say.
任何竞选者都不会说这些话
Anyone running for office wouldn't dare utter those words.
每一个幕僚  顾问和下属
Every advisor and consultant and staff member
都不希望总统候选人说这种话
would beg a presidential candidate not to say them.
但我可以说
But I can say them.
因为2016年
Because I will not be seeking
我将不参与总统竞选
the Democratic nomination in 2016.
候选人都谨言慎行
Candidates are cautious.
他们含糊其辞  回避周旋  小心翼翼
They must equivocate. They dodge and tiptoe.
但我更愿离开这间办公室时  能完成有价值的事
But I'd rather leave this office having accomplished something of value
而不是为了再任四年而无所作为
than secure another four years having done nothing at all.
富兰克林·德拉诺·罗斯福提出新政
Franklin Delano Roosevelt ushered in an era of hope and progress
让美国走向希望和进步的时代
when he proposed the New Deal.
当时  他的改革被认为很激进
And at the time, his reforms were considered radical.
但他说  "这个国家需要进行
But he once said, "This country demands bold,
大胆而执着的实验
persistent experimentation.
想办法  试一试很正常
It is common sense to take a method and try it.
如果失败了  坦白承认  然后重新来过
And if it fails, admit it frankly and try another.
但重要的  是要尝试"
But above all, try something."
罗斯福比谁都明白
Roosevelt would have understood better than anyone
尝试特别办法的必要性
the necessity for trying something different.
新政成功了那么多年
The New Deal succeeded for many years,
但在新政失效前  我们得尝试更新的东西
but we must now try something newer before it fails us.
如果《美国就业法案》成功了
If America Works succeeds,
我们将彻底改造美国梦
we will reinvent the American dream.
如果我们的尝试失败
If we fail in our attempt,
我们会坦白承认  然后重新来过
we will admit it frankly and try another.
但重要的  是要尝试
But above all, we must try something.
谢谢  天佑美利坚合众国
Thank you, and God Bless the United States of America.
现在是凌晨2点
It's two in the morning.
是啊  我刚离开白宫
Yeah, I just left the White House.
新闻发布会  电话  邮件
The press conference, phone calls, emails,
其它的明天再说
the rest can wait until tomorrow.
-你睡了吗  -还没
- Were you asleep? - No.
这地方不错
This is a cool place.
租金多少
How much is your rent?
你不是说《美就法》暂停了吗
I thought you said AmWorks was on hold.
当时确实是  现在不是了
Well, it was and then it wasn't.
领导层不想让他参选
The leadership didn't want him to run.
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?
没人  但我猜这是他那番讲话的唯一理由
Nobody. But I figure it's the only reason he'd make that speech.
-但他仍会参加竞选吧  -他说不会
- He's still gonna run though, isn't he? - He says he's not.
我永远都比你更了解他  赛斯
I know him better than you ever will, Seth.
他不可能不参选
There's no way he doesn't run.
这是你来的原因吗  因为他需要我帮他
Is that why you're here? Because he needs my help now?
不  我就是想亲自来看看你的状况
No, I just-- I wanted to check up with you in person this time.
-是他要你来的  -是
- He asked you to. - Yes.
不过我把你的邮件发给他了
I did send him your email, though.
-他说什么  -我不确定他看过没
- What did he say? - I'm not sure if he's read it.
你是不是该睡觉了
You should probably get some sleep, huh?
明天可是新闻团队的大日子
Big day for the press team tomorrow.
你可以回禀说我活得好好的
You can report back. Alive and well.
我时不时来看你一眼可以吗
Is it okay if I stop by now and then?
我有的选吗
Do I have a choice?
我没有  但是我又不能逼你开门
I don't, but I can't force you to open the door.
随便你了
Whatever you want.
多谢
Thanks.
再见
I'll see you soon.
邓巴女士
Ms. Dunbar.
总统先生
Mr. President.
上次我们谈话时我心事重重
I had a lot on my mind when we last spoke.
-昨晚的演讲  -是一个重大决定
- The speech last night, it was-- - Yes, it was a big decision
如果我之前显得心不在焉  我很抱歉
and I apologize if I was distracted.
-没事的  -来谈谈无人机袭击案
- Not at all, sir. - So, the drone strike case.
你一直在走国家机密的抗辩策略
You've been pursuing the State secrets defense.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
-希瑟  我能这样称呼你吗  -请便
- Heather-- May I call you Heather? - Please.
美国人民反感秘密
The American people are sick of secrets.
这就是我昨晚竭力想说明的
That's the point I was trying to make last night.
我承诺给大家真相  现在就要履行诺言
I promised the truth, and now we're going to deliver.
是什么真相  先生
What truth is that, sir?
一名美国公民被炸断了腿
A man had his legs blown off. An American citizen.
我们要承认
We're going to own up to that.
承认是中情局实施了那次无人机袭击
We're going to admit that the CIA conducted the drone strike
-并且解释原因  -这些信息是机密
- and explain the reasons why. - That information is classified.
不再是了
Not anymore.
我准许你  公开机密
You have my permission to make the classified brief public.
先生  这么做在法律上不合理
Sir, that is not a sound legal approach.
但这正是这个国家所需要的
But it's what the country needs.
我们不是在向国家抗辩
We're not appealing to the country.
-而是九个大法官  -错
- We're appealing to nine justices. - Wrong.
我们要承担责任  一石二鸟地博得好感
We're appealing to both by taking responsibility.
是  有人被炸残  他家人被杀
Yes, a man was maimed, his family members were killed.
但因此  成百上千的生命得以获救
But hundreds, perhaps thousands of lives were saved as a result.
我明白这种情感逻辑
I understand the emotional logic,
-但我们不能...  -你坐在那儿对我说
- but we can't-- - You sat right there and told me
-就连最高法院法官也会心软  -对  但
- even Supreme Court justices have hearts. - Yes, but--
我不能告诉你怎么做好你的工作
Far be it from me to tell you how to do your job.
我这一生中  从未做过律师
I've never practiced law a day in my life.
但我书写法律
But I have written them.
我占着这间办公室  我知道国家需要什么
And occupying this office, I know what the country needs.
它需要了结
It needs closure.
我去写新的抗辩了
Let me work on a new argument.
-谢谢  希瑟  -谢谢  总统先生
- Thank you, Heather. - Thank you, Mr. President.
总统夫人  您想把它们放在哪
Where do you want these, ma'am?
只要不是这里  哪都行
Anywhere. Just not in here.
好
Okay.
-斯科特 -怎么了
- Scott? - Yes?
这儿还有一些
Here's a couple more.
*让城镇从你身边漂过*
*Let the towns drift slowly by
*听铁路车轮哼鸣*
*Listen to the steel rails hummin'*
*这就是流浪者的催眠曲*
*That's a hobo's lullaby*
*别为明天担忧*
*Do not think about tomorrow*
*让明天来  任明天去*
*Let tomorrow come and go*
*今晚你睡在温暖的车厢*
*Tonight you've got a nice warm boxcar*
想不想来份花生酱果冻三明治
You want a peanut butter and jelly?
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
一切都还好吗
Is everything all right?
我想做联合国大使  弗兰西斯
I want the UN job, Francis.
参议院两周后就休会了
The Senate goes home in two weeks.
我要你进行休会任命
I want a recess appointment.
我为此做了准备  我能胜任
I prepared for it. I can do this.
等一切结束后
And after it's all over,
如果我成功胜任我知道我能胜任的工作
if I've done the job I know I can do,
我今后做什么都行了
I'll be positioned for anything I want.
克莱尔
Claire--
我和白宫法律顾问确认过了
Now, I checked with the White House Counsel.
在提名被否决后
There is precedent for a recess appointment
有休会任命的先例
after a rejected nomination.
只有一次  但你肯定不是首例
Only once, but you wouldn't be the first.
我知道你在政治上会遭非议
And I know you'll take a hit politically.
我也清楚人们会认为我不配
And I know people will think I don't deserve it.
他们对我会心存顾虑
They'll have doubts in me.
可如果我们只能走到这一步了呢
But what if... this is as far as we get?
如果18个月后一切都将结束
What if it's all over in 18 months?
我不想等  也不想屈就
I don't want to wait, or settle for something else,
-尤其是我已经投入了这么多...  -好吧
- when I've put all this work into-- - Okay.
我会做的
I'll do it.
-你确定不来半块  -我不饿
- You sure you don't want half? - I'm not hungry.
如果你找我  我在书房
I'll be in my study.
美国第二任总统约翰·亚当斯的夫人阿比盖尔·亚当斯
在美国独立革命时期和建国后夫君担任总统期间
一直以挚友和参谋的身份
在国家事务上给予约翰·亚当斯宝贵的意见和建议
富兰克林·罗斯福总统的第一夫人
埃莉诺·罗斯福一直坚持拥有独立的事业追求
成为第一夫人后还继续作为教师承担教学工作
同时坚持不懈地推动美国社会在人权和妇女权益方面的进步
罗斯福总统过世后  埃莉诺继续为自己的信仰和追求进行着不懈的努力
1945年  她被杜鲁门总统任命为美国首位驻联合国大使
后还成为联合国人权委员会的首任主席
她被认为是美国历史上最伟大的第一夫人
希拉里·克林顿是现代美国历史上
第一位在白宫西区拥有自己办公室的第一夫人
比尔·克林顿刚刚当选总统后  便力排众议
破天荒地委任自己的第一夫人来领导医疗改革
希拉里虽满腔热情
但她主导的医疗改革被国会山上的议员们打得片甲不留  惨败收场
但这没有让希拉里放弃自己的政治野心
离开白宫后  她先是成功当选纽约州参议员
继而参加了2008总统大选  虽然最后没有战胜奥巴马
但是虽败犹荣  并受命担任了奥巴马政府的国务卿
在目前美国两党紧锣密鼓地筹备2016总统大选之际
几乎所有人都认同  希拉里不仅是民主党中最有实力的潜在候选人
而且面对共和党对手也有着巨大的优势
美国政府部门大部分重要岗位的人事任命  不仅需要总统提名
还需要参议院经过听证会质询后  投票任命才能生效
当总统特别希望提名某人担任某个职位
而此人得不到议员们的认可和支持时
白宫有时候会利用参议院处于休会状态时进行提名
从而避开参议院听证这一步  让提名人直接上任
但这种"休会任命"如果经常发生  不仅会引起国会反弹
也会给选民一种不尊重民主制度的印象
2012年  奥巴马曾通过"休会任命"的手段任命了四名政府官员
但该任命在2014年被美国最高法院判定为违宪